<application>
  <component name="AppStorage">
    <histories>
      <item value="display categories of the current level on the page without this current category" />
      <item value="categories of the same level are displayed without the current" />
      <item value="Настройка email отправки" />
      <item value="File not exist" />
      <item value="Sending AJAX data from the data submission form" />
      <item value="category for search page" />
      <item value="исправление багов" />
      <item value="Related Categories block show child category" />
      <item value="Answer and Clarification: The principle subject of The Shortcoming in Our Stars is love. In the novel, John Green inspects various types of adoration" />
      <item value="Answer and Explanation: The main theme of The Fault in Our Stars is love. In the novel, John Green examines different kinds of love" />
      <item value="content to be changed utilizing programming interface spinbot" />
      <item value="text to be changed using api spinbot" />
      <item value="not AJAX" />
      <item value="way" />
      <item value="Once arrow form html" />
      <item value="AY: 2019/20 CIS5006 - Mobile and Web Technologies Term 2 Module Leader: Catherine Tryfona Assessment Brief Assessment Title: Developing Mobile and Web Apps to Support Global Health WRIT1 HAND-OUT DATE: 21 February 2020 HAND-IN DATE: 3 April 2020 Contents Learning Outcomes 3 EDGE 3 Assessment Requirements / Tasks (include all guidance notes) 3 Assessment Criteria 5 Submission Details 7 Feedback 7 Marking Criteria 8 Additional Information 11 Referencing Requirements (Harvard) 11 Mitigating Circumstances 11 Unfair Practice 11 Learning Outcomes This assessment is designed to demonstrate a student’s completion of the following Learning Outcomes: Design and develop mobile and web applications from a given specification using appropriate programming languages and frameworks. Compile documentation that will indicate evidence of design and testing their application. Assess abd contrast the challenges of developing mobile and Web applications compared to other platforms. EDGE The Cardiff Met EDGE supports students in graduating with the knowledge, skills, and attributes that allow them to contribute positively and effectively to the communities in which they live and work. This module assessment provides opportunities for students to demonstrate development of the following EDGE Competencies: Assessment Requirements / Tasks (include all guidance notes) This assessment is worth 100% of your module marks. During the sessions, you will design and develop both a web application (using JavaScript etc.) and a mobile application (using Xamarin in Visual Studio) to address an agreed real-world problem in the following area: Child and Maternal Health Given the complex area of mHealth, your applications should take into account principles of good UI design, and should show consideration for ethics and information security. In the final week of seminars, you will demonstrate both of your applications. You will draw on your experiences to produce a 4,000 word equivalent report that addresses the following for both your web and mobile applications: An introduction to your project idea and its rationale. The design and development processes that you undertook, including protoyping images. Consideration for legal and ethical issues in the design and development of your apps. An overview of the final applications. Evidence of testing and critical evaluation. An assessment and comparison of both the challenges and benefits of developing both mobile and web applications. Appendicies containing code listings. The structure and presentation of your report is up to you but it should be of a professional standard and clearly laid out in a report format. You should also include Harvard Referencing throughout. Assessment Criteria Submission Details Please see Moodle for confirmation of the Assessment submission date. Submission will be by 4:00pm on the deadline day. Any assessments submitted after the deadline will not be marked and will be recorded as a Non-Attempt. The assessment must be submitted as a pdf / word document through the Turnitin submission point in Moodle Your assessment should be titled with your Student ID Number, module code and assessment id, e.g. st12345678 CIS5003 WRIT1 Feedback Feedback for the assessment will be provided electronically via Moodle, and will normally be available 4 working weeks after initial submission. The feedback return date will be confirmed on Moodle. Feedback will be provided in the form of a rubric and supported with comments on your strengths and the areas which you improve. All marks are preliminary and are subject to quality assurance processes and confirmation at the Examination Board. Further information on the Academic and Feedback Policy in available in the Academic Handbook (Vol 1, Section 4.0) Marking Criteria Additional Information Referencing Requirements (Harvard) The Harvard (or author-date) format should be used for all references (including images). Further information on Referencing can be found at Cardiff Met’s Academic Skills website. Mitigating Circumstances If you have experienced changes or events which have adversely affected your academic performance on the assessment, you may be eligible for Mitigating Circumstances (MCs). You should contact your Module Leader, Personal Tutor or Year Tutor in the first instance. An application for MCs, along with appropriate supporting evidence, can be submitted via the following link to the MCs Dashboard Applications for MCs should ideally be submitted as soon as possible after circumstances occur &amp; at the time of the assessment. Applications must be submitted before the relevant Examination Board. Further information on the Mitigating Circumstances procedure is available in the Academic Handbook (Volume 1, Section 5) Unfair Practice Cardiff Metropolitan University takes issues of unfair practice extremely seriously. The University has distinct procedures and penalties for dealing with unfair practice in examination or non-examination conditions. These are explained in full in the University's Unfair Practice Procedure (Academic Handbook: Vol 1, Section 8) Types of Unfair Practice, include: Plagiarism, which can be defined as using without acknowledgement another person’s words or ideas and submitting them for assessment as though it were one’s own work, for instance by copying, translating from one language to another or unacknowledged paraphrasing. Further examples include: Use of any quotation(s) from the published or unpublished work of other persons, whether published in textbooks, articles, the Web, or in any other format, which quotations have not been clearly identified as such by being placed in quotation marks and acknowledged. Use of another person’s words or ideas that have been slightly changed or paraphrased to make it look different from the original. Summarising another person’s ideas, judgments, diagrams, figures, or computer programmes without reference to that person in the text and the source in a bibliography or reference list. Use of services of essay banks and/or any other agencies. Use of unacknowledged material downloaded from the Internet. Re-use of one’s own material except as authorised by the department. Collusion, which can be defined as when work that that has been undertaken with others is submitted and passed off as solely the work of one person. An example of this would be where several students work together on an assessment and individually submit work which contains sections which are the same. Assessments briefs will clearly identify where joint preparation and joint submission is specifically permitted, in all other cases it is not. Fabrication of data, making false claims to have carried out experiments, observations, interviews or other forms of data collection and analysis, or acting dishonestly in any other way." />
      <item value="fucked up a fucking feature" />
      <item value="TODO finish the item with the category output if no child categories are found" />
      <item value="страницы тегов" />
      <item value="Running Homebrew as root is extremely dangerous and no longer supported. As Homebrew does not drop privileges on installation you would be giving all build scripts full access to your system." />
      <item value="Add redirect for flashcard category" />
      <item value="this array can contain category names, slugs or even IDs" />
      <item value="The Database Collate type. Don't change this if in doubt" />
      <item value="исправил работу нижнего блока перелинковки" />
      <item value="check the box to display the block at the bottom of the page" />
      <item value="gets the front page id set in options" />
      <item value="we remove the actions hooked on the '__after_loop' (post navigation)" />
      <item value="Chain" />
      <item value="Display WordPress content directory" />
      <item value="The number of posts for posting in one day" />
      <item value="columt" />
      <item value="the variable deduces from the csv file the value from the third column" />
      <item value="SPECIFY ALL in argument(2) TO SELECT ALL CSV FILE SPEAKERS" />
      <item value="no post search method selected" />
      <item value="was successfully insert to table" />
      <item value="was successfully insert" />
      <item value="post data with id" />
      <item value="id post data with" />
      <item value="I execute a database query" />
      <item value="Work with exporting posts content to sql database table" />
      <item value="slug child category" />
      <item value="Redirect if 'category_redirect' is set" />
      <item value="title output filter with the addition of {s} at the end if there is no such character" />
      <item value="Add a page number if necessary" />
      <item value="Filters wp_title to print a neat &lt;title&gt; tag based on what is being viewed." />
      <item value="tag under old WP" />
      <item value="names of taxonomies for which you need to add the following fields" />
      <item value="id plays the role of a field name prefix" />
      <item value="set the table to $ wpdb if it is not" />
      <item value="Start backend for adding settings to the page for editing taxonomy elements" />
    </histories>
    <option name="languageScores">
      <map>
        <entry key="ENGLISH" value="268" />
        <entry key="BULGARIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="POLISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="RUSSIAN" value="268" />
        <entry key="FINNISH" value="1" />
        <entry key="NORWEGIAN" value="1" />
        <entry key="SERBIAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="UKRAINIAN" value="2" />
        <entry key="ITALIAN" value="1" />
      </map>
    </option>
  </component>
  <component name="Settings">
    <option name="googleTranslateSettings">
      <google-translate>
        <option name="primaryLanguage" value="RUSSIAN" />
      </google-translate>
    </option>
    <option name="ignoreRegExp" value="" />
  </component>
</application>